mail-signatures.com 2019-03-25

# Privacy Policy - Mail-Signatures.com

In CodeTwo, we care deeply about the privacy and security of your data. This Privacy Policy will help you understand what data we collect, what we use it for and how you can exercise your rights.

We abide by the following principles while processing your data:

  * we do not collect more information than it is necessary;
  * we do not use your data for purposes other than those specified in this Privacy Policy;
  * we do not keep your data if it is no longer needed;
  * we do not disclose your data in cases other than these specified in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies to services offered through mail-signatures.com. **Our website contains links to other websites. Once redirected to a website outside of our domains, this Policy is no longer applicable**.

## Summary

You can browse our website without giving away any information about you other than your IP address. If you decide to post a comment on our blog you will be asked to provide your personal details such as your name and your email. Our website uses cookies to collect anonymous and aggregated statistical data about users’ visits on our website and to advertise our products online. You can find more information about cookies and types of data we collect when you use our website in _What information do we collect and when?_ _s_ section.

Once you decide to contact us you will be asked to provide your personal details such as your name and your email. We will use this data communicate with you. You can find more information about how we process your data once you decide to contact us in _Contacting us_ section.

You have a right to access your data, a right to have information about you corrected or deleted. If processing of your data is based on consent you also have the right to withdraw it at any given time. Withdrawal of your consent will not influence the lawfulness of processing based on this consent before its withdrawal. We will not use your data for the purposes of automated decision-making or profiling. You can find more information about your rights in _What are your rights?_ _section._

If you want to exercise your rights or have any other questions relating to this Privacy Policy you can contact us using [this form](https://www.codetwo.com/form/security-officer/).

## What information do we collect and when?

Unless you decide to contact us or post a comment on our blog, you can browse our website without giving away any information about you other than your IP address. Recording of your IP address is necessary for technical purposes related to administration of our servers. We will also use your IP address to collect general, statistical information about you (e.g. to get information about the region from which you connect with our website). We will not be able to identify you based only on your IP address.

If you decide to post a comment on our blog you will be asked to provide your personal details such as your name and your email. You cannot post a comment without giving away this information about you.

We do not record any of the information that you fill in when using our Signature Generator and we do not use it for any purposes. We will, however, record some anonymous information about you (using the so-called ‘cookies’) if you generate a signature using Signature Generator and we will use it to advertise our products online, as described below.

Our website supports the so-called ‘cookies’, which are small files containing information saved to your hard drive. We use cookies for several purposes:

  *  **to collect anonymous and aggregated statistical data about users’ visits on our website.** We use this data to analyze how our website is used and to improve it using Google Analytics and/or other web traffic analytics tools.
  *  **to advertise our products online.** We use tracking and remarketing cookies from Google AdWords, Google Analytics, Facebook Conversion Tracking and Facebook Custom Audiences to advertise our products online. We make use of all targeting features available in Google AdWords including: demographic and location targeting, remarketing, affinity audiences, custom affinity audiences, in-market audiences, similar audiences  ([learn more about cookies used in ads by Google](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/) [and about cookies used by Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/) ). You can customize Google Display Network advertisements using the [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) or block it by installing Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on.

 **Unless you set up your internet browser (e.g. Mozilla Firefox or Google Chrome) not to accept cookies, it will accept the use of them.** You can always disable cookies in your browser’s preferences even if you have consented to the use of cookies in the past. You may also delete cookies stored on your computer at any given time. Please note that disabling cookies may negatively impact your online experience on CodeTwo website and prevent you from using certain website or logging in to our web applications.

### Contacting us

Although you can use our website without giving away information about you, once you decide to contact us you will be asked to provide your personal details such as your name and your email address. We will use this data to communicate with you. We will delete your data once your matter is solved and information about you is no longer needed.

You are not obliged to give us any of the information above, but if you decide not to give it to us or provide us with false or incorrect information we may be unable to respond to your message.

## What are your rights?

### Access to data

You have the right to access the information that we have on you. You can do this using [this form](https://www.codetwo.com/form/security-officer/).

We will make sure to provide you with a copy of the data we process about you. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to give us some additional information that we will use to verify your identity. If you fail to provide such information and the information that you have already given to us is not sufficient to identify you, we may refuse to provide you with information.

We will fulfill your request by sending your copy electronically, unless the request expressly specifies a different method. For any subsequent access request, we may charge you with an administrative fee.

### Erasure and rectification of data

If you believe that the information we have about you is incorrect, you are welcome to contact us so we can update it and keep your data accurate.

We will automatically delete information about you after it is no longer needed for the purposes it was collected. If at any point you wish for us to delete information about you, you can do this by contacting us using [this form.](https://www.codetwo.com/form/security-officer/)

### Withdrawal of consent

If processing of your data is based on consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. If you at any point wish to withdraw your consent, you can do this by contacting us using [this form](https://www.codetwo.com/form/security-officer/). Remember that withdrawal of consent will not affect the lawfulness of processing based on this consent before its withdrawal.

### Profiling

We do not use any information provided by you for the purposes of automated decision-making, including profiling.

## Disclosure of your data

We guarantee that all your personal information is protected, and that we will not make this information available to third parties in cases different than those specified below, unless you give us a permission to do so or unless such disclosure is necessary to comply with a legal obligation that is imposed on us.

We will not disclose your data to any entities located in countries outside of the European Economic Area unless appropriate data protection standards are fulfilled.

We may share information that you provided us with when contacting us with:

  * our legal advisors to the extent that such disclosure is necessary to obtain legal advice or protect our rights in legal proceedings;
  * governments and law enforcement authorities only if we are required to do so by law. We will always attempt to redirect the law enforcement agency or government to request any data directly from you. If compelled to disclose your data, we will promptly notify you and provide a copy of the demand.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We constantly review our Privacy Policy and strive towards making it better. That is why we reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will not reduce any of your rights stated in this Privacy Policy without asking for explicit prior consent to the changes. Each amendment to the Privacy Policy will be signed with the date of publishing and will be effective since that date.

## How to contact us and seek additional help?

If you have any questions or doubts related to this Privacy Policy or want to know more about how we protect your personal data or your rights, [contact us](https://www.codetwo.com/form/security-officer/).

We hope that we will be able to answer all your questions and settle all disputes amicably. Nonetheless, if you think that your rights were not observed or that your privacy was harmed, you can always lodge a complaint with the Polish Data Protection Authority which supervises our operations.

CodeTwo is a limited partnership (CodeTwo sp. z o.o. sp. k.) established under the laws of the Republic of Poland. You can find our full contact details [here](https://www.codetwo.com/company/contact).

Effective date: 2018-02-28
